<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Workshop / event landing page on Helmholtz Imaging Workshop Template</title><link>https://helmholtz-imaging.github.io/workshop-template/</link><description>Recent content in Workshop / event landing page on Helmholtz Imaging Workshop Template</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://helmholtz-imaging.github.io/workshop-template/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>My awesome workshop</title><link>https://helmholtz-imaging.github.io/workshop-template/overview/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://helmholtz-imaging.github.io/workshop-template/overview/</guid><description>Introduction What this presentation provides:
Demo page for Helmholtz Imaging workshops based on markdown format Examples of special elements which can be used in a presentation Presentation metadata The frontmatter of a workshop markdown file provides metadata used to print the title slide.
Slide separation Slides in markdown are separated by --- lines.
Headers Subheaders Use markdown headers to define slide headers. A table of content will automatically be rendered from the first header on each slide.</description></item><item><title>Subtutorial about layouts</title><link>https://helmholtz-imaging.github.io/workshop-template/tutorial-layout/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://helmholtz-imaging.github.io/workshop-template/tutorial-layout/</guid><description>Introduction This tutorial is introducing a few very basic alignment helpers for this framework.
Horizontal alignment Use the horizontal shortcut&amp;hellip;
.. to display two items next to each other.
Blocks Use the block shortcut&amp;hellip;
.. to bring two items into one block, for example to display them below each other in a horizontal layout.
Centering .. horizontally Use the center shortcut to display something horizontally centered. Centering .. horizontally and vertically Use the center-center shortcut to display something horizontally and vertically centered.</description></item><item><title>Post 3</title><link>https://helmholtz-imaging.github.io/workshop-template/posts/post-3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 11:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://helmholtz-imaging.github.io/workshop-template/posts/post-3/</guid><description>Occaecat aliqua consequat laborum ut ex aute aliqua culpa quis irure esse magna dolore quis. Proident fugiat labore eu laboris officia Lorem enim. Ipsum occaecat cillum ut tempor id sint aliqua incididunt nisi incididunt reprehenderit. Voluptate ad minim sint est aute aliquip esse occaecat tempor officia qui sunt. Aute ex ipsum id ut in est velit est laborum incididunt. Aliqua qui id do esse sunt eiusmod id deserunt eu nostrud aute sit ipsum.</description></item><item><title>Post 2</title><link>https://helmholtz-imaging.github.io/workshop-template/posts/post-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://helmholtz-imaging.github.io/workshop-template/posts/post-2/</guid><description>Anim eiusmod irure incididunt sint cupidatat. Incididunt irure irure irure nisi ipsum do ut quis fugiat consectetur proident cupidatat incididunt cillum. Dolore voluptate occaecat qui mollit laborum ullamco et. Ipsum laboris officia anim laboris culpa eiusmod ex magna ex cupidatat anim ipsum aute. Mollit aliquip occaecat qui sunt velit ut cupidatat reprehenderit enim sunt laborum. Velit veniam in officia nulla adipisicing ut duis officia.
Exercitation voluptate irure in irure tempor mollit Lorem nostrud ad officia.</description></item><item><title>Post 1</title><link>https://helmholtz-imaging.github.io/workshop-template/posts/post-1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 09:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://helmholtz-imaging.github.io/workshop-template/posts/post-1/</guid><description>Tempor proident minim aliquip reprehenderit dolor et ad anim Lorem duis sint eiusmod. Labore ut ea duis dolor. Incididunt consectetur proident qui occaecat incididunt do nisi Lorem. Tempor do laborum elit laboris excepteur eiusmod do. Eiusmod nisi excepteur ut amet pariatur adipisicing Lorem.
Occaecat nulla excepteur dolore excepteur duis eiusmod ullamco officia anim in voluptate ea occaecat officia. Cillum sint esse velit ea officia minim fugiat. Elit ea esse id aliquip pariatur cupidatat id duis minim incididunt ea ea.</description></item></channel></rss>